<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ShoeStore</string>
    <string name="shoe_store">Shoe Store</string>
    <string name="shoe_lists">SHOE LISTS</string>
    <string name="shoe_details">SHOE DETAILS</string>
    <string name="email">EMAIL</string>
    <string name="password">PASSWORD</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="register">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="instruction_msg">INSTRUCTIONS</string>
    <string name="welcomeTextLine1">Welcome to Shoe Store, where your shoe shopping experience begins! Step into a world of style, comfort, and quality as you explore our diverse collection of footwear. Whether you\'re on the hunt for the latest fashion trends, seeking the perfect pair for a special occasion, or simply looking for everyday comfort, our store is your destination for all things footwear.
    </string>
    <string name="welcomeTextLine2">At Shoe Store, we pride ourselves on offering a curated selection of shoes that blend fashion and function. We invite you to embark on a journey of discovery, where every step you take brings you closer to the perfect pair of shoes. Welcome to the ultimate shoe shopping experience!
    </string>
    <string name="instructionTextLine1">Step into a shopping experience like no other at Shoe Store, where we\'ve not only curated an extensive range of footwear but also enhanced your shopping journey with user-friendly features. Explore the convenience of viewing a comprehensive list of shoes, each meticulously categorized to cater to various tastes and preferences. Our thoughtfully organized selection ensures that you can effortlessly browse through the latest styles or find timeless classics with ease.
    </string>
    <string name="instructionTextLine2">But that\'s not all – we\'ve also empowered you to become a part of our growing shoe community. With just a few clicks, you can input details such as the shoe\'s name, size, description, brand, and even include an image. Welcome to a shoe shopping experience that goes beyond the ordinary – your journey starts here!
    </string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="add">+</string>
    <string name="shoe_name">SHOE NAME</string>
    <string name="shoe_size">6.5</string>
    <string name="shoe_brand">SHOE BRAND</string>
    <string name="shoe_description">SHOE DESCRIPTION</string>
    <string name="welcome">WELCOME</string>
    <string name="logout">LOGOUT</string>
    <string name="logout_success">LOGOUT SUCCESSFUL</string>
    <string name="enter_name">SHOE</string>
    <string name="enter_image_name">IMAGE</string>
    <string name="enter_company">COMPANY</string>
    <string name="enter_description">DESCRIPTION</string>
    <string name="enter_size">SIZE</string>
    <string name="submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="cancel">CANCEL</string>
    <string name="add_new_shoe">Add new shoe</string>
</resources>
